const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: 'In the Moroccan Christmas Party episode, Michael creates an “original” drink consisting of Orange Juice and Vodka. What does he call it?',
    answers: [
      'Screwdriver',
      'One of Everything',
      'Orange Vod-juice-ka',
      'Happy Naval'
      ],
    correctAnswer:'Orange Vod-juice-ka'
  }, 
  {
    question: 'How long does it take Michael to brush his teeth?',
    answers: [
      '1 minute',
      '10 seconds',
      '30 seconds',
      '3 minutes'
      ],
    correctAnswer: '10 seconds'
  },
  {
    question: 'At Jim\s BBQ, Michael and Jim sing what song together on karoake?',
    answers: [
      'That One Night',
      'Coming to America',
      'Islands in the Stream',
      'The Little Drummer Boy'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Islands in the Stream'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which member of the former Stamford branch was imprisoned for insider trading?',
    answers: [
      'Tony',
      'Karen',
      'Josh',
      'Martin'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Martin'
  },
  {
    question: 'What day did Kelly and Ryan finally totally hook up?',
    answers: [
      'February 13th',
      'December 24th',
      'February 14th',
      'October 3rd'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'February 13th'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of subs does Michael bring in for the office on his birthday?',
    answers: [
      'Ham, olive, onion',
      'Bologna, tomato, ketchup',
      'Peanut butter and jelly',
      'Tuna, ranch, pepper jack'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Bologna, tomato, ketchup'
  },
  {
    question: 'In response to Andy\'s attempted blackmail, what does Robert California refer to himself to?',
    answers: [
      'The Godfather',
      'The One',
      'The Alpha',
      'The Lizard King'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Lizard King'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the invention that the US Military buys from David Wallce for $10MM dollars?',
    answers: [
      'Suck it!',
      'Lick it!',
      'Quit it!',
      'Bop it!'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Suck it!'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the bluetooth Pam and Jim use to communicate all day with?',
    answers: [
      'Toshiba X-3',
      'Matsuhashi B-400',
      'Sony Infinite 58',
      'Samsung Esquire'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Matsuhashi B-400'
  },
  {
    question: 'Temporary branch manager - Deangelo Vickers - once had a goal to start an Animal Olympics. What did he say happened that halted this goal?',
    answers: [
      'Life happened',
      'Lack of funding',
      'Hates dogs',
      'Semi-pro basketball abroad'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Life happened'
  }
];